- Penny, hello.
- Hey, Sheldon.
(Sheldon:)What is shaking?
(Penny:)I'm sorry?
(Sheldon:)It's colloquial. A conversation opener.
(Sheldon:)So do you find the weather satisfying?
(Sheldon:)Are you currently sharing in the triumph
of some local sports team?
PENNY: What's wrong with you?
You're freaking me out.
(Sheldon:)I'm striking up a casual conversation
with you.
What's up?
(Penny:)Please don't do that.
(Sheldon:)But I'm given to understand that when
you have something awkward to discuss...
(Sheldon:)...it's more palatable
to preface it with banal chitchat.
(Penny:)So this wasn't the awkward part?
(Sheldon:)No.
(Penny:)Oh. All right.
What's up?
SHELDON:
Oh, good, I used that right.